https://www.cityofchesapeake.net/06administration/privacy-policy.htm

Library
Geographic Information Systems (GIS)
Chesapeake Television
Watch Live!
On Demand Video
Program Schedule
Visitors
Visiting Chesapeake?
Get Your Permit Online
Public Facilities Manual (PFM)
Watch Meeting Live
Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)
Voting
Where do I vote?
Who is my Legislator?
share
print > City of Chesapeake, Virginia > Administrative pages > City of Chesapeake Website Privacy Policy
City of Chesapeake Website Privacy Policy
It is the policy of the Commonwealth of Virginia and the City of Chesapeake that personal information about you will be collected only to the extent necessary to provide the service or benefit desired; that only appropriate information will be collected; that you shall understand the reason the information is collected and be able to examine their personal record which is maintained by a public body.
Gathering Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to the City of Chesapeake websites may choose to interact in ways that require the City of Chesapeake to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information gathered depends on the nature of the interaction. In each case, the City of Chesapeake collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction. The City of Chesapeake does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Cookies
A cookie is a tiny piece of text that is placed on your computer's hard drive. If your browser is set to notify you before accepting a cookie, you will receive a request for a cookie to be stored on your computer. We do not use cookies to record any personal information. Cookies may be used by some City web applications to pass needed information from one page to the next. We want to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you. We analyze user traffic patterns on our web portal from information automatically provided by your browser when you visit our site. We use the statistical information gathered to measure site and server performance and continually improve the content of our sites to better serve you.
Embedded Content
Some pages on www.CityofChesapeake.net may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, forms, etc.) Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking and monitor your interactions with the embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged into that website. This policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they share and/or collect here. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Third-Party Applications
The City of Chesapeake uses third-party applications in order to provide online transactions such as requesting a service, improve site performance, offer better service or make various transactions easier.
Records Retention and Freedom of Information Act Laws
Public records will be retained in accordance to records retention laws and provided to the public in accordance with the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA).
Note that information you provide via this website may be kept and provided to the public. Learn more about your rights and our responsibilities under FOIA.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, the City of Chesapeake may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in the City of Chesapeake's discretion.
We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to the Privacy Policy.
City Hall Address:
Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)
Policies
Privacy Policy
Accessibility
© Copyright 1996 - 2018 • City of Chesapeake • All rights reserved
